Guide to the Office of the Secretary, Yale University, Annual Reports Submitted to the President
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1990-1991; Accession 1994-A-008
  - Nursing, School of, Judith B. Krauss, 1991 September (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecolgy, Frederick Naftolin, M.D., 1992 April (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Ophthalmology and Visual Science, Marvin L. Sears, M.D., 1991 September (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Organization and Management, School of, Virginia Condon, 1991 August (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Orthopaedics and Rehabilitation, Gary E. Friedlaender, 1992 July (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Pathology, Jon S. Morrow, 1992 January (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Peabody Museum of Natural History, Alison F. Richard, 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Pediatrics, Joseph Warshaw, M.D., 1991 November (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Pharmacology, Leonard K. Kaczmarek, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Philosophy, J.A. Hartigan, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Physics, Michaet E. Zeller, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Police, Allan Guyet, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Political Science, William J. Foltz, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Psychiatric Institute, Thomas H. McGlashan, M.D. combined with Psychiatry, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Psychiatry, Benjamin S. Bunney, M.D., 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Religious Studies, Robert R. Wilson, 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Renaissance Studies, George K. Hunter, 1991 November (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Saybrook College, James A. Thomas, 1991 July (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Edward Stankiewicz, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Social and Policy Studies, Institution of, Joseph LaPalombara, 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Sociology, Kai Erikson, 1991 October (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, Roberto Gonzalez Echevarria, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Statistics, J.A. Hartigan, 1991 August (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Surgery, William F. Collins, Jr., M.D., 1991 December (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Teacher Preparation and Placement, 1991 September (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1992 April (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Timothy Dwight, Robert Farris Thompson, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Trumbull College, Harry B. Adams, 1991 June (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Yale Law Report, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Yale-New Haven, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 92)
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1991-1992; Accession 1995-A-020
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2028
  - American Studies Program, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Department of Anesthesiology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Department of Anthropology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Department of Applied Physics, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - School of Architecture, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Department of Astronomy, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Athletics, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Berkeley College, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Department of Biology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Branford College, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bush Center in Child Development and Social Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Department of Cell Biology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Department of Cellular and Molecular Physiology, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Department of Chemistry, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Child Study Center, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Department of Chemical Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Department of Classics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Department of Comparative Literature, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Section of Comparative Medicine, School of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Department of Computer Science, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Office of Cooperative Research, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Council on East Asian Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Davenport College, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Department of Dermatology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Department of Diagnostic Radiology, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - School of Drama, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Department of East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Department of Economics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Department of Electrical Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Department of English, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Department of Film Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Film Study Center, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Department of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - French Department, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Department of Genetics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Department of Geology and Geophysics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Graduate School, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Yale University Health Services, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Department of History, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Department of the History of Art, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Department of the History of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Institute of Sacred Music, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Department of Internal Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Center for International and Area Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Department of Italian Languages and Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Program in Judaic Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Department of Laboratory Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Language Laboratory, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Law School, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Department of Linguistics, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Department of Mechanical Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - School of Medidne, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Medieval Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Department of Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry Research Report, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Morse College, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - School of Music, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Department of Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Section of Neurobiology, School of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Department of Neurology, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - School of Nursing, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Department of Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Ofice of Research AflFairs Grant and Contract Administration, School of Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Department of Operations Research, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Department of Ophthalmology and Visual Science, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - School of Organization and Management, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Department of Pathology, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Peabody Museum, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Department of Pediatrics, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Pediatric Medicine, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Department of Pharmacology, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Department of Philosophy, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Department of Physics, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Department of Political Science, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Yale Psychiatric Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Department of Psychiatry, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Department of Religious Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Program in Renaissance Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Department of Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Department of Sociology, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Department of Spanish and Portuguese, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Department of Statistics, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Department of Surgery, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Yale-New Haven Teacher Institute, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Teacher Preparation Program, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Department of Therapeutic Radiolog, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Trumbull College, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Undergraduate Career Services, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - University Health Services, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 96)
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1992-1993; Accession 1996-A-019
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  - AMERICAN STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ANTHROPOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - APPLIED PHYSICS, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ARCHAEOLOGICAL STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ARCHITECTURE, SCHOOL OF, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ASTRONOMY, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ATHLETICS, PHYSICAL EDUCATION and RECREATION, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - BIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - BIOSPHERIC STUDIES, INSTITUTE OF, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - BOYER CENTER FOR MOLECULAR MEDICINE, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CELL BIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
  - CELLULAR and MOLECULAR PHYSIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 12)
  - CHAPLAIN, OFFICE OF THE, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 13)
  - CHEMISTRY, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 14)
  - CHILD STUDY CENTER, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 15)
  - CLASSICS, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 16)
  - COMPARATIVE LITERATURE, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 17)
  - COMPARATIVE MEDICINE, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 18)
  - COMPUTER SCIENCE, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 19)
  - DAVENPORT COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 20)
  - DERMATOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 21)
  - DIAGNOSTIC RADIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 1A, Folder 22)
  - DIVINITY SCHOOL, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - DRAMA, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - DWIGHT, TIMOTHY COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - EAST ASIAN LANGUAGES and LITERATURES, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - ECONOMIC GROWTH CENTER, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - ECONOMICS, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - ENGINEERING: CHEMICAL, COUNCIL, ELECTRICAL, MECHANICAL, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 29-29C)
  - ENGLISH, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - EPIDEMIOLOGY AND PUBLIC HEALTH, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - FILM STUDIES PROGRAM, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - FRENCH, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - FORESTRY AND ENVIRONMENTAL STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - GENETICS, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - GEOLOGY AND GEOPHYSICS, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - GRADUATE SCHOOL, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - HEALTH SERVICES CENTER, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - HISTORY, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - HISTORY OF ART, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - HISTORY OF MEDICINE, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - IMMUNOBIOLOGY, SECTION OF, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - INTERNAL MEDICINE, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - INTERNATIONAL AND AREA STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - ITALIAN LANGUAGE AND LITERATURE, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - INVESTMENT COMMITTEE, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 46)
  - JONATHAN EDWARDS COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 47)
  - JUDAIC STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 48)
  - LABORATORY MEDICINE, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 49)
  - LANGUAGE LAB, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 50)
  - LAW SCHOOL, 1992-1993 (Box 3A, Folder 51)
  - LINGUISTICS, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - MATHEMATICS, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - MEDICINE, SCHOOL OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - MOLECULAR BIOPHYSICS AND BIOCHEMISTRY, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - MORSE COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - MUSIC, DEPARTMENT OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - MUSICAL INSTRUMENTS, COLLECTION OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - NEAR EASTERN LANGUAGES AND CIVILIZATIONS, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - NEUROBIOLOGY, SECTION OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - NEUROLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - NURSING, SCHOOL OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - OBSTETRICS AND GYNECOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - OFFICE OF RESEARCH AFFAIRS, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - OPHTHALMOLOGY AND VISUAL SCIENCES, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - ORGANIZATION AND MANAGEMENT, SCHOOL OF, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - PATHOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - PEABODY MUSEUM, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - PEDIATRICS, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - PHARMACOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - PHILOSOPHY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - PHYSICS, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - POLICE DEPARTMENT, UNIVERSITY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - POLITICAL SCIENCE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - PSYCHIATRIC INSTITUTE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - PSYCHIATRY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - RELIGIOUS STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - RENAISSANCE STUDTES, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - SACRED MUSIC, INSTITUTE OF, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - SAYBROOK COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - SILLIMAN COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - SLAVIC LANGUAGES AND LITERATURES, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - SOCIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - SPANISH AND PORTUGUESE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - STATISTICS, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - SURGERY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - TEACHERS INSTITUTE, YALE-NEW HAVEN, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - TEACHER PREPARATION AND PLACEMENT, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - THERAPEUTIC RADIOLOGY, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - TRUMBULL COLLEGE, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - WOMEN'S STUDIES, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 91)
- Annual reports submitted to the president, 1986-1996; Accession 1999-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - American Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesiology, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Applied Physics, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archaeological Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Architecture, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Astronomy, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Athletics, Physical Education, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Boyer Center for Molecular Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Branford: College, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Calhoun College, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cell Biology, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cellular and Molecular Physiology, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chaplain, Office of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chemical Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chemistry, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Child Study Center, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Classics, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Comparative Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Comparative Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cooperative Research, Office of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Council of Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Davenport College, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dermatology, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Drama, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - East Asian Languages and Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - East Asian Studies, Council on, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Economics, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - English, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ezra Stile College, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Film Studies Program, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Forestry and Environmental Science, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - French, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Genetics, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Germanic Languages, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Graduate School, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Health Services, University, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - History, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - History of Art, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - History of Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Immunobiolog y, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Internal Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Italian Languages and Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Jonathan Edwards College, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Judaic Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Language Lab, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Law School, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Linguistics, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Management, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Mathematics, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Medicine, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Medieval Studies Program, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Music, Department of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Lit., 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Neurology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Nursing, School of, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Office of Research Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Ophthalmology and Visual Sciences, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Pathology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Peabody Museum, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Pediatrics, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Pharmacology, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Philosophy, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Physics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Police Department, University, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Political Science, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Psychiatric Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Psychiatry, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Religious Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Renaissance Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Sacred Music, Institute of, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Silliman College, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Slavic Languages and Lit., 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Sociology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Spanish and Portuguese, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Surgery, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Teacher Preparation and Placement, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Trumbull College, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Women's Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Yale College, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Yale-New Haven Teachers Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Yale Athletics, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Child Study Center, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Pathology, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Psychology, 1986-1995 (Box 6, Folder 99)
- Annual reports for departments and schools, 1994-2000; Accession 2002-A-193
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - American Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anesthesiology, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Architecture, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Art School, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biology -Molecular, Cellular, and Dev., 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biology -Molecular, Cellular, and Dev., 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Boyer Center Molecular Med, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Branford College, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - British Art Center, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bush Center Child Develop, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Calhoun College, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Calhoun College, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cell Biology, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cell Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Chemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Child Study Center, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Comparative Literature, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Comparative Literature, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Comparative Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Comparative Medicine, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Computer Science, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Davenport College, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dermatology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Diagnostic Radiology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Drama School, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - East Asian Lang/Lit, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - English, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Epidemiology and Pub Health, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Institute for Biospheric Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Inst Soc/Policy Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - International/Area Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Language Lab, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Molecular Biophysics/Biochemistry, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Neurology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Nursing School, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Opthalmology, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Orthopaedics and Rehab, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Peabody Museum, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Economic Growth Center, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Electrical Engineering, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - English, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Epidemiology and Pub Health, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Genetics, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Geology/Geophysics, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Germanic Lang/Lit, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - History of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - History of Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Inst of Sacred Music, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Inst Soc/Policy Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Internal Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Laboratory Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Language Lab, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Law School, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Linguistics, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Mathematics, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Medical School, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Molecular Biophysics/Biochemistry, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Near Eastern Lang/Lit, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Neurobiology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Nursing School, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Opthalmology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Pathology, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Peabody Museum, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Pediatrics, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Pediatrics, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Pharmacology, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Philosophy, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Physics, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Political Science, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Psychiatry, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Psychiatry, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Religious Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Sociology, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Statistics, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Therapeutic Radiology, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Timothy Dwight College, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Trumbull College, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - University Librarian, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - International Security, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - African/Am Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - American Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Anesthesiology, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Applied Physics, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 89)